Guide to the Mickey Neylan Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Mickey Neylan papers
1892-1979
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
4518
4518-001
Neylan, Mickey
.84 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
Papers of an employee of the International Typographical Union Local #202, Seattle
Employee of the International Typographical Union Local #202, Seattle. Her brother was Harry E.B. Ault.
Correspondence, publications, writings, ephemera, labor union and Socialist pamphlets, labor union song books, newsletters, clippings, photographs; 1897-1979. In part, records of Seattle Typographical Union, Local 202. Included also is an autobiography and a few other papers of Harry E.B. Ault, including material regarding his newspaper, the Seattle Union Record. Neylan's personal papers include documentation about Equality Colony in Skagit County, Washington.
Open to all users.
Donated by Justice and Georgia Griffin, 2/17/1995
The visual materials that form part of this collection are described and indexed in
A Guide to the
.
Inventory/container list available in Special Collections.
Neylan, Mickey$vArchives; Ault, Harry E. B.$q(Harry Erwin Bratton),$d1883-1961; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Equality Colony (Skagit County, Wash.); Brotherhood of the Co-operative Commonwealth.; International Typographical Union.$bLocal 202 (Seattle, Wash.)
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor; Labor History; Labor Unions; Seattle
- Seattle Typographical Union. Local 202
  - Organizational Features, 1945-46, 70 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Incoming Letters, 1928-70 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Outgoing Letters, 1934 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Financial Records, 1892-1970 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Newsletters, 1932-83 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Newsletters Of Others, 1966 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Notes, undated (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Business Cards, undated (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Photographs, undated (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Ephemera, 1957-74 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Contracts, 1917-70 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Membership Records, 1967, 69 (Box-folder 1/12)
  - Clippings, undated (Box-folder 1/13)
- Ault, Harry E.B.
  - Biographical Features, 1964 (Box-folder 1/14)
  - Writings - Autobiography, undated (Box-folder 1/15)
  - Subject Series – Seattle Union Record, 1929-73 (Box-folder 1/16-17)
- Personal Papers
  - Incoming Letters, 1969-79 (Box-folder 1/18)
  - Photographs, 1909-67 (Box-folder 1/19)
  - Clippings, 1909-79 (Box-folder 1/20)
  - Subject Series – Equality Colony/brotherhood Of The Co-Operative Commonwealth, 1897-1968 (Box-folder 1/21)
  - Pamphlets, 1903-70 (Box-folder 2)